[Music]
So let's move on to your situation where I don't have
access to the MPs in most
cases
and what is your prime
over your status are
you but you can find it on YouTube feeling about what your
status and actions are but you ca
n't and began to think of writing every what your expected reward is right so full your bleeding
and things like date turn people office which over again so what is started of
right and they are not gts ...
sum of everything but give me 17 give
what I do start date again in
example
date gives me d value it
status
one right so can I use this
submission
good sample per way of yashwant
same is tha fine
pea where I come from waste you as one and
as prime test one
presenting things are which marker so I can do this so what is what
essential what I should generated
rejectly first
look at jo d status aate akar in d
transaction and give after date take d sum
of d rewards date I get and you set as
n sample so what I do is n fixed
policy I am not going right dr sudoku
code per this please look it up in d book I am
going to fix n policy five
generate multiple projects ok and use
date you well you policy
of techniques
where and Samsung
you get d samples right I have d model and
run transactions on date I get this
samples and use date you update the value
function so this is also
and so this is note  A tax method on
policy
evaluation policy
of cost
without d real system don't give you an
infinite supply of how and something but I give
you an simulation model
so what I mean by simulation model
of you have written programs you play games
play card games
black jacket and example
really
okay it's like d movie par 21
everyone
seen d movie 21 don't worry I am not going you
play d movie
and give start turning over dear card and
give they have you make sir they get 21 possible
opponent is
you can cup going if you want and stop right
you stop before I share opponent's card
rights a very simple cup going and he is what are
d actions
give me
d continue and stock
very simple problem right but no if you want you
think of it as okay what is d
probability was
this what is d probability
because I have
turned over
newly hit comment  By
what chords you are already flipping I
ask you to write a computer program
dat bill play 21 with me and black jack with
me it's a
family straight forward think write it need you pick
track of which card you have
delt and give random please sample from
dat card and give it I don't I can write
program dat bill play
blackjack with me match match so give
actually writing a program dat
bill compute that ps prime
write so model and tomorrow simulation model and
sample model ok generate samples but they are
note an full specification of d
transaction probabilities
with example ho
you use that sample model you compute my
translation I can just leave d sample
of the nice things about motocorrect a
one think which I want you to note every is and
d sample set draw with d transactors
and every note only pick d state dat I bill be
doing valuation
also give me d value with which I bill be
doing d valuation right this  This
expectation right, whether expectation
computation date is also determined by d sample
letter
let take care when they
travel using d per peaking d status but
updating was using this within
evaluation right using d model but every d
transaction here note only give me d
state but also give me d robot with which
time updating d value of d state
want take and policy value
question date you want me to
test the same it sold be
interested in evaluating d file
while you need to do one
small additional think possible i have an
fixed price no greedy no nothing
business ok no exploration business i
explore d policy bill change
d price
give this note no anchor p right i come
today
interested in d small subset give they
sufficient per me you start in
transactions only from date small subset
reminder
start from h and every state because
it's a deterministic policy right i  have
no guarantee dat d status would be only
specific rejectly dear bill b following right this
no guarantee dat d status dat i don't
start from bill ever b widgeted per
me you get samples from dat so i have to
start from
my different status so dat i can get
samples from concrete status ok so infact if just
take policy you have to do this
exploring starters because there is no
guarantee dat you bill hit every state and with
desirous policy
happiness you be something dat loves you take
stage
completely random policy every state pick and
action with probability half an
action and half a state and pick action
probability on bhaiya
[music] [
music]
provide it d interest
award
so everything goes n start
from every and ko and if i am
baking random let no where i ko you this
part of d world
red i start from every and if n
acting completely random please no where i
bill  to you this part of d world so there not
reachable from one so if
you need you fear and ways of doing it
n on smaller problems but bigger
and larger problems wikam not very
attractive right n so you can you take me
dynamical systems they can you take me
physics you can you techniques your
defending on what is this d setup date you
are interested
[music]
so give a sample model
expect
from
updating b value of ok so what you every I said
next state after ssc one and
we can consider date rejectly starting
from s one right
yes
probability of transaction return
policy
I am every d simple example so I have yes only
one action from yes
ok 20% of d time is
possible
handle
ok tree
what about
opinion
[music]
cup going unlimited
zero one
[music]
you do it if you use every
occurrence of d state
it's called every visit  Import n tomorrow so when I say
he d first account what did it mean so I take
d return
occurring after date right and think I said
you one sample on updating people of it
every visit date means take d return after
every accurate e so right so d first
return bill b this match right and d second
return bill b him you bill b this match okay so
what is the d real problem every is
date when I do every visit I have just
taken in one sample tractor
price
[music] hey
till one project
respect is not very important you know if don't remember why very
unexpected out never hut of
bikes
out date in d limit right if you do a lot
and lot of samples in this particular
how items both d se elif function
according to you me trip in next date
according to you see lover and give reward
according to you d expected award so one's own
lot of civilization so I
specifically projectry is no upper  So yes yes yes one s two s
three s four base ho me
times this kid of an think akar should be
determined me rolling d dick again and
again rolling m coins again what ever right
tasting d coins again and again but I didn't do that
I just generated this
one sample once and I was saying okay so this
part is one sample no this part is another
sample this part is another sample on one roll
of d de and just taking multiple sub
sections of it and giving repeated using
it so if I have
started from yes her and
read and d experiment but I not just let me remember if you are actually once
every million please no it is happen tis
every interested
significant change
double d problem so that
thoughts same it jumped be n problem
you think everywhere se jumped be n problem
model sex
[praise]